Guide to the Laura Foreman Papers 1949-2001 MSS 122
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Video, 1973-1985; 41.25 linear feet 33 Paige Cartons
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - a deux - NYSCA, 1978 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0185)
      Alternate Title: a deux
    - Heirlooms; a deux, 1977 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0186)
      TRT: [approx. 25 minutes]
    - Songandance; Locrian, 1973 (Box 135, Media ID: 122.0187)
      TRT: [approx. 60 minutes]
    - Fantasy / Teddy Bears, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0188)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy Teddy Bear Shots
    - Fantasy / Dummies Reel #1, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0189)
      Alternate Title: Dummies Reel #1
    - Fantasy / Dummies Reel #2, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0190)
      Alternate Title: Dummies Reel #2
    - Fantasy / Prop Room Tape #1, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0191)
      Alternate Title: Tape #1 Laura in Prop Room
    - Fantasy / Prop Room Tape #2, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0192)
      Alternate Title: Laura in Prop Room
    - Fantasy / Dressing Room at Japan House, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0193)
      Alternate Title: Satoru at Japan House, the Marpetts #1
    - Fantasy / Laura Talking to Mirror Tape #1, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0194)
      Alternate Title: Schtict Tape #1
    - Fantasy / Laura Talks to Mirror Tape #2, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0195)
      Alternate Title: Schtict Tape #2
    - Fantasy / Laura Talking to Herself, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0196)
      Alternate Title: Laura's Schtict Tape #3 & #4
    - Fantasy / Mirror Shots Tape I, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0197)
      Alternate Title: Mirror Shots Tape I
    - FANTASY / Mirror Shots Tape #2, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0198)
      Alternate Title: Mirror Tape II
    - Fantasy; Poster Tape 1, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0199)
      Alternate Title: Poster Shots #1
    - Poster Tape 2, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0200)
      Alternate Title: Poster Tape #2
    - 19th St. Shot, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0201)
    - 19th St., 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0202)
      Alternate Title: 19th Street Front Steps and Upstairs
    - Fantasy - Japan House I, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0203)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Reel I
    - Japan House 2, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0204)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Reel II
    - Japan House III & Barre Shots, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0205)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Reel III and Fantasy Shots Tape 5
    - Barre Shots and Playground I, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0206)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy - Playground Tape I
    - Playground II, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0207)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy - Playground Tape II
    - Installation I, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0208)
      Alternate Title: Installation #1
    - Installation 2 / Satoru's Loft, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0209)
      Alternate Title: Installation #2
    - Installation / Poetry, 1978 (Box 136, Media ID: 122.0210)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy Shots of Laura Upstairs
    - Saturo at Bar Talking About His Life - Dub #1, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0211)
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - Laura / Mirror, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0212)
      Alternate Title: Japan House #2
    - Original Snow & Dances - Tape #2, undated (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0213)
      Alternate Title: Roof Section - Applause and Close-up
    - Original Snow Shot, undated (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0214)
    - Original Snow Shot #3, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0215)
      Alternate Title: Snow Shot, Roof Section, Close-ups, Barre Section
    - Tape Recorder Shot, 1979 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0216)
      Alternate Title: Recycle
    - Satoru Dancing Roof Section at Angle, undated (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0217)
    - Documentary Edit & Snow Shot / Stephen Backer, undated (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0218)
      Alternate Title: Laura Foreman Dance Theatre Documentary
    - Laura Foreman Interview, undated (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0219)
      Alternate Title: LFDT Tape #1 Gertrude Stein Piece
    - Auditions (Women) & Laura at Loft, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0220)
    - Auditions (Women's) #1, 1977 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0221)
    - Men's Auditions #1, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0222)
    - Men's Auditions #2, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0223)
    - Male Auditions #3, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0224)
    - LFDT Audition Callback Tape #1, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0225)
    - LFDT Audition Callback Tape #2, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0226)
    - Rehearsal #1, undated (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0227)
    - Rehearsal #2 & Loft Lookover, 1978 (Box 137, Media ID: 122.0228)
    - Laura Loft looking, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0229)
      TRT: [approx. 18 minutes]
    - Annie in Office, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0230)
    - Laura Looking at Lighting in Satoru's Loft / Luncheonette, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0231)
    - Laura at Parsons #2, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0232)
    - Laura at New School #1, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0233)
    - Laura at Parsons #3 & Laura at New School #4, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0234)
    - Ward-Nasse Gallery / John & Laura Doing NYSCA Application, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0235)
    - Laura and John Doing NYSCA Application, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0236)
    - Lecture Demonstration at Baruch College, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0237)
    - Cathy Abbott and Barbara Buckner - Audition Tape, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0238)
    - Manuel Carvalho Audition Tape #1, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0239)
    - Manuel Carvalho Audition Tape #2, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0240)
    - Mark Graff Audition Tape #1, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0241)
      Alternate Title: John and Satoru Rehearsing Fragments and "UPS"
    - Mark Graff Audition Tape #2, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0242)
      Alternate Title: John and Satoru rehearsing Fragments and "UPS"
    - Jeff Bush and Celia Ipiotis Audition, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0243)
      Alternate Title: John and Satoru rehearsing "UPS"
    - Greg Tonning Audition Tape, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0244)
    - Louis Jaffe Audition Tape, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0245)
    - Satoru and Laura at Hoarty's Studio Tape #1, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0246)
    - Laura at Hoarty's Studio Tape #2, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0247)
    - Burlesque Tape, 1977 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0248)
    - Laura Poetry Reading #1, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0249)
    - Laura Poetry Reading #2, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0250)
    - Franklin Furnace #1, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0251)
    - Franklin Furnace #2, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0252)
    - LFDT; NEA Grant Tape - Dub, 1978 (Box 138, Media ID: 122.0253)
      Alternate Title: "Heirlooms" & "a deux"
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape I Section II, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0254)
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape II Section II, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0255)
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape III Section III, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0256)
    - a deux; Cubiculo; Tape IV, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0257)
    - a deux #1, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0258)
    - a deux #2, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0259)
    - a deux #3, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0260)
    - a deux #1 1974 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0261)
    - a deux #2 1974 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0262)
    - Postludes and a deux; "Live" ATL, 1975 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0263)
      TRT: [approx. 23 minutes]
      Alternate Title: Postludes and a deux
    - Heirlooms - Original Edit, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0264)
      TRT: 00:12:00
      Alternate Title: Heirlooms
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #1, 1977 (Box 22, Media ID: 122.0265)
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #2, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0266)
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #3, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0267)
    - Heirlooms Rehearsal #4, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0268)
    - Heirlooms - Costume Tape, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0269)
    - Laura Foreman - #6, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0270)
    - Laura Foreman - #7, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0271)
    - Laura Foreman - #8, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0272)
    - Heirlooms - Tape #9, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0273)
    - Heirlooms - Tape #10, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0274)
    - Heirlooms - Tape #7, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0275)
    - Heirlooms - Section 1 with Lights; 5/5/1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0276)
      TRT: 00:25:04
    - Heirlooms - 2nd Section with Lights, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0277)
      TRT: 00:15:39
    - Heirlooms - 3rd Section with Lights (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0278)
    - Heirlooms - Section One, First Intermission, 1977 (Box 139, Media ID: 122.0279)
      TRT: 00:24:07
    - Heirlooms - Section Two - Straight (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0280)
      TRT: 00:16:13
    - Heirlooms - Section Three - Straight, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0281)
      TRT: 00:23:36
    - Roxanne Talks Her Heirlooms Part - Tape 1, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0282)
    - Roxanne Talks Her Heirlooms Part - Tape 2 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0283)
    - Satoru & Roxanne - Heirlooms, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0284)
    - Roxanne's Part - Heirlooms, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0285)
    - Heirlooms Act II - Satoru and Roxanne, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0286)
    - Heirlooms - Additional Notes for Roxanne, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0287)
    - Heirlooms Act III - Satoru & Roxanne, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0288)
    - Laura's Part & Snapshots, 1977 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0289)
    - Ward-Nasse "Program" #1, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0290)
      Alternate Title: Program
    - Ward-Nasse "Program" #2, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0291)
    - Program, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0292)
    - Program #1, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0293)
    - Program #2, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0294)
    - Laura Foreman Interview, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0295)
    - Monopoly - Video I, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0296)
    - Monopoly - Video II, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0297)
    - Monopoly in Soho, 1976 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0298)
    - City of Angels - Delacorte Theater / New York Dance Festival, 1975 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0299)
    - City of Angels - Wollman Hall, 1975 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0300)
    - City of Angels - "Live", 1975 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0301)
    - City of Angels - Barnard College, 1974 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0302)
    - City of Angels - Left Angled Audience View Version, 1975 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0303)
    - City of Angels - Audience View Version, 1975 (Box 140, Media ID: 122.0304)
    - [1]--Nancy's Part of City [2]-- Still Life, 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0305)
    - Spaces - MOMA, 1973-1974 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0306)
    - Spaces - Edit Dub, 1973 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0307)
    - Corrected version of Locrian / Spaces, 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0308)
    - Locrian version of Spaces at Moma, 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0309)
    - Locrian at ATL, 1973 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0310)
    - ATL Version of Locrian, 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0311)
      Alternate Title: Locrian
    - Glass and Shadows - No Media, 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0312)
      TRT: 00:19:08
    - Glass and Shadows - With Media & Lighting, 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0313)
      TRT: 00:20:23
    - Glass and Shadows, 3/7/75 - Choreography Only (Copy), 1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0314)
      TRT: 00:18:52
    - songandance #1, 1973 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0315)
      Alternate Title: songandance
    - songandance #2, 1973 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0316)
    - Signals, 5/17/1975 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0317)
      TRT: 00:17:15
      Alternate Title: Signals
    - Signals - MOMA, 1973 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0318)
    - postludes - at New School, 1974 (Box 141, Media ID: 122.0319)
      Alternate Title: postludes
    - [1]-- Fantasy / Poetry Installation [2]-- Poetry Reading #1 [3]-- Poetry Reading #2, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0320)
      TRT: [approx. 40 minutes]
    - [1]-- Mug Shot Tape #1 [2]-- Mug Shot Tape #2 [3]-- Arp Room, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0321)
    - [1]-- Arp Room #2 [2]-- MF Arp Room Tape #1 [3]-- MF Arp Room Tape #2, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0322)
    - [1]-- MF Arp Room Tape #3 [2]-- Enteries Tape #1 [3]-- Enteries Tape #2 [4]-- Enteries Tape #3, 1976, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0323)
    - [1]-- Enteries Tape #4 [2]-- Enteries Tape #5 [3]-- Enteries Tape #6, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0324)
    - [1]-- Enteries Tape #7 [2]-- Enteries Tape #8 [3]-- Enteries Tape #9, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0325)
    - [1]-- Enteries Tape #10 [2]-- Enteries Tape #11 [3]-- Enteries Tape #12, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0326)
    - [1]-- Enteries Tape #12 - Last Take [2]-- Enteries Tape #13 [3]-- Enteries Tape #14 [4]-- Enteries Tape #15, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0327)
    - [1]-- Enteries 16 Documentary [2] Enteries 17 Documentary [3]-- Enteries 18 Documentary, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0328)
    - [1]-- Satoru Rehearsing [2]-- China's China [3]-- Laura Construction [4]-- Satoru Rehearsing, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0329)
    - [1]-- Satoru Dancing [2]-- 6/28 Dance [3]-- Satoru on Floor, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0330)
    - [1]-- Satoru on Floor, cont. [2]-- Wall dance [3]-- Satoru Rehearsing [4]-- Hound Dog, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0331)
    - [1]-- Sarabande Rehearsal Tape [2]-- Go Rehearsal Tape [3]-- Go Movements Rehearsal Tape, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0332)
    - [1]-- Hound Dog & 19th St. Shots [2]-- Satoru at Kitchen Tape #1 of 5 [3]-- Rehearsal, 1978, undated (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0333)
    - [1]-- Mark Fisher Audition tape [2]-- Jim Vito Audition Tape [3]-- Barbara Laurence/ Barbara Jousen Audition Tape, 1978 (Box 142, Media ID: 122.0334)
    - [1]-- Satoru Marking Out Sequences [2]-- Tripod Test Tape [3]-- Satoru Opening Gifts, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0335)
    - [1]-- Satoru Upset & Laura's Response [2]-- Satoru Warming Up [3]-- Satoru at Barre, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0336)
    - [1]-- Satoru at Barre, cont. [2]-- Satoru Talking About His Life [3]-- Mug Shots [4]-- Snow Shot Tape #1, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0337)
    - [1]-- Snow Shot Tape #2 [2]-- Snow Shot Tape #3 [3]-- Snow Shot Tape #4, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0338)
    - [1]-- Snow Shot Ruth Tape #1 [2] Snow Shot Fred Tape #1 [3]-- Snow Shot Buy Take [4]-- Snow Shot M. Fisher, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0339)
    - [1]-- Satoru at Kitchen #1 [2]-- Performance - Audience [3]-- Janice and Annie Setting Up, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0340)
    - [1]-- Japan House #1 [2]-- Japan House #2 [3]-- Japan House #3, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0341)
    - [1]-- Japan House #4 [2]-- Japan House #5 [3]-- Japan House #6, undated (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0342)
      TRT: [approx. 50 minutes]
    - [1]-- Japan House #7 [2]-- Japan House #8 [3]-- Satoru's Kitchen Concert #2 [4]-- Satoru's Kitchen Concert #3, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0343)
    - [1]-- Satoru at the Kitchen #4 [2]-- Satoru at the Kitchen #5, 1978 (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0344)
      TRT: [approx. 45 minutes]
    - [1]-- Heirlooms Act I - Intermission [2]-- Heirlooms Intermission - Act II, undated (Box 143, Media ID: 122.0345)
    - [1]-- Heirlooms Act I Experiment [2]-- Heirlooms Act III Scene II [3]-- Heirlooms Act II Experiment, undated (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0346)
    - [1]-- Heirlooms Act III Scene II - Experimental [2]-- Ghost Shot, undated, 1978 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0347)
    - Document of Rehearsal at Cubicullo - a deux, 1974 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0348)
    - Program, 1976 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0349)
    - Program - entire dance, 1976 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0350)
    - Program - Ward-Nasse Gallery, 1976 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0351)
    - Spaces, 1973 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0352)
    - [1]-- Wollman Hall Tape #2 [2]-- Wollman Hall Tape #1 [3]-- Wollman Hall Last Take, 1978 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0353)
    - Wollman Hall Tape - Badly Recorded, 1978 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0354)
    - [1]-- Wollman Hall Pan Spaces [2]-- Wollman Hall Pan From Elevator [3]-- Wall Section Tape #3, 1978 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0355)
    - [1]-- Original Snow & Dances [2]-- Original Snow Shot [3]-- Snow Shot & Roof Section, undated, 1978 (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0356)
    - [1]-- Snow Shot, cont. [2]-- Tape Recorder Shot [3]-- Satoru Dancing Roof Section [4]-- Snow Shot, undated (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0357)
    - Steven Backer's List of Dances, undated (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0358)
    - [1]-- Steven Backer's List of Dances [2]-- Laura at Baruch College, undated (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0359)
    - Laura at Baruch College & Rehearsal, undated (Box 144, Media ID: 122.0360)
    - Dub of Parts of Laura Foreman's Performance, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0361)
    - [1]-- Dub of Parts of Laura Foreman's Performance [2] 127, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0362)
    - [1]-- Laura Foreman Interview [2]-- End of Women's Audition, 1978 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0363)
    - [1]-- Lighting Part II [2]-- Women's Audition Part II [3]-- Men's Audition Beginning, 1978 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0364)
    - [1]-- Men's Audition II [2]-- Men's Audition III, 1978 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0365)
    - [1]-- Audition Callback Men & Women I [2]-- Audition Callback Men & Women II [3]-- Rehearsal #1, 1978 (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0366)
    - [1]-- Last Part of S & L in Loft [2]-- Loft Look Over [3]-- 5th Ave. Loft, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0367)
    - [1]-- S. Rehearsing and Misc. Shots [2]-- Lighting Discussion Continued, 1978, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0368)
    - [1]-- #141 Dub [2]-- #142 Dub, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0369)
    - [1]-- #143 Dub [2]-- #144 Dub (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0370)
    - [1]-- #145 Dub [2]-- #146 Dub, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0371)
    - [1]-- #147 Dub [2]-- #148 Dub, undated (Box 145, Media ID: 122.0372)
    - a deux - Master Edit, 1977 (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0373)
      TRT: 00:09:15
    - [1]-- #149 Dub [2]-- #150 Dub, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0374)
    - [1]-- #150 Dub, cont [2]-- #151 Dub [3]-- #152 Dub [4]-- #153 Dub, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0375)
    - [1]-- #153 Dub, cont [2]-- #154 Dub [3]-- #155 Dub, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0376)
    - [1]-- #156 Dub [2]-- #157 Dub, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0377)
    - [1]-- #158 Dub Poetry Reading [2]-- #159 Dub Poetry Reading [3]-- #160 Dub B. College, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0378)
    - [1]-- #160 Dub, cont. [2]-- #161 Dub, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0379)
    - [1]-- #162, Re-zeroed [2]-- #163, undated (Box 146, Media ID: 122.0380)
    - [1]-- #164 Dub [2]-- #165 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0381)
    - [1]-- #165 Dub, cont [2]-- #166 Dub [3]-- #167 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0382)
    - 168 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0383)
    - #169 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0384)
    - [1]-- #170 Dub [2]-- #171 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0385)
    - #172 a deux Edit Dub, 1974 (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0386)
      TRT: 00:16:00
    - [1]-- #173 a deux Dub II [2]-- #174 Dub (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0387)
    - #175 Heirlooms Dubs, 1977 (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0388)
    - #176 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0389)
    - #177 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0390)
    - #178 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0391)
    - [1]-- #179 Dub [2]-- #180 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0392)
    - [1]-- #188 Dub, cont [2]-- #181 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0393)
    - #182 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0394)
    - [1]-- #181 Dub, cont [2]-- #183 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0395)
    - [1]-- #182 Dub, cont [2]-- #184 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0396)
    - #185 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0397)
    - [1]-- #186 Dub [2]-- #191 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0398)
    - Heirlooms III - Dup, 1977 (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0399)
    - [Heirlooms Section I - Dup], 1977 (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0400)
    - #198 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0401)
    - #199 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0402)
    - #200 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0403)
    - [1]-- #201 Dub [2]-- #202 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0404)
    - [1]-- #202 Dub, cont [2]-- #203 Dub [3]-- #204 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0405)
    - [1]-- #204 Dub, cont [2]-- #205 Dub, undated (Box 147, Media ID: 122.0406)
    - #206 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0407)
    - [1]-- #207 Dub, cont [2]-- #208 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0408)
    - [1]-- #208 Dub, cont [2]-- #209 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0409)
    - [1]-- #209 Dub, cont [2]-- #210 Dub [3]-- #211 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0410)
    - [1]-- #211 Dub, cont [2]-- #212 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0411)
    - [1]-- #212 Dub, cont [2]-- #213 Dub [3]-- #215 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0412)
    - #214 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0413)
    - [1]-- #216 City Dub [2]-- #217 City Dub, 1975 (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0414)
    - [1]-- #217 Dub, cont [2]-- #218 Dub [3]-- #219 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0415)
    - [1]-- #219 Dub, cont [2]-- #220 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0416)
    - [1]-- #221 Dub Part I [2]-- #222 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0417)
    - [1]-- #222 Dub, cont [2]-- #225 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0418)
    - [1]-- #226 Dub, cont [2]-- #227 Dub [3]-- 122.0228 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0419)
    - [1]-- #229 Dub [2]-- #230 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0420)
    - [1]-- #230 Dub, cont [2]-- #232 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0421)
    - [1]-- #232 Dub, cont [2]-- #233 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0422)
    - [1] #234 Dub [2]-- #235 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0423)
    - [1]-- 236 Dub [2]-- 173 Part I Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0424)
    - [1] #235 Dub, cont [2]-- #221 Dub Part II [3]-- #236 Dub, undated (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0425)
    - Untitled NYSCA Work Tape #2, 1978 (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0426)
    - Art/Video/Sound - Tape I, 1979 (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0427)
    - Focal Ingenuity, 1988 (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0428)
      TRT: 00:08:22
    - Shacks of America, 1988 (Box 148, Media ID: 122.0429)
      TRT: 00:07:05
    - Unknown #1, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0430)
    - Unknown #2, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0431)
    - Unknown #3, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0432)
    - Unknown #4, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0433)
    - Unknown #5, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0434)
    - Unknown #6, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0435)
    - Unknown Sony 30 #1, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0436)
    - Artichoke For Two, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0437)
    - Fresh - Reg Dens., undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0438)
    - Unknown / Blank, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0439)
    - Sony Virgin Tape #1, 1980 (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0440)
    - Sony Virgin Tape #2, 1980 (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0441)
    - Unknown 3M Tape, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0442)
    - Unknown Sony 30 #2, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0443)
    - Unknown Sony 30 #3, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0444)
    - Unknown Scotch Scratch Tape, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0445)
    - Unknown Sony 60 #1, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0446)
    - Unknown Sony 60 #2, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0447)
    - Unknown Sony Scratch Tape #1, 1978 (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0448)
    - Unknown Sony Scratch Tape #2, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0449)
    - Unknown Sony Scratch Tape #3, undated (Box 149, Media ID: 122.0450)
    - AFI Master With Uncorrected Audio, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0451)
    - Reel II 1st Half, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0452)
    - AFI - Test Dub, 1978 (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0453)
    - First Part of AFI Master, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0454)
    - Unknown Sony 60 #3, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0455)
    - Unknown Sony 60 #4, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0456)
    - Unknown Sony 60 #5, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0457)
    - Unknown Sony 60 #6, undated (Box 150, Media ID: 122.0458)
- Series VII: Film